[
  {
    "question": "مادر",
    "pronounce": "Maadar",
    "answer": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "پدر",
    "pronounce": "Padar",
    "answer": "father"
  },
  {
    "question": "اب",
    "pronounce": "Ob",
    "answer": "water"
  },
  {
    "question": "شیر",
    "pronounce": "Sheer",
    "answer": "milk"
  },
  {
    "question": "بله",
    "pronounce": "Baa-leh",
    "answer": "yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "خیر",
    "pronounce": "Khayr",
    "answer": "no"
  },
  {
    "question": "سلام",
    "pronounce": "Salam",
    "answer": "hello"
  },
  {
    "question": "نام",
    "pronounce": "Naam",
    "answer": "name"
  },
  {
    "question": "کجا",
    "pronounce": "Koja",
    "answer": "where"
  },
  {
    "question": "خانه",
    "pronounce": "Khonah",
    "answer": "home"
  },
  {
    "question": "خوش آمدی",
    "pronounce": "Khush Amadi",
    "answer": "welcome"
  },
  {
    "question": "خداحافظ",
    "pronounce": "Khoda Hafiz",
    "answer": "goodbye"
  },
  {
    "question": "حال شما چطور است",
    "pronounce": "Haaleh shoma chetor asti",
    "answer": "how are you"
  },
  {
    "question": "اسم شما چیست",
    "pronounce": "Esme shoma chist",
    "answer": "what's your name"
  },
  {
    "question": "دوستت دارم",
    "pronounce": "Doste darem",
    "answer": "i love you"
  },
  {
    "question": "نمیدانم",
    "pronounce": "Nemidanam",
    "answer": "I dont know"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساعت چند است",
    "pronounce": "Sa'at chand ast",
    "answer": "what time is it"
  },
  {
    "question": "من گم شدم",
    "pronounce": "Man gom shodam",
    "answer": "im lost"
  }
]